这就是你们上周 呜呜呜
This is what you... (Indistinct)
last (Indistinct)...
我想回医学院
I'm thinking about
going back to medical school.
Jimmy医生 哈
Dr. Jimmy, huh?
我们在庆祝Fiona即将成为医生夫人了
We're celebrating Fiona's
impending marriage to a doctor.
喔 真的
Oh, wow. Really?
-你们可以和我一起去  -去密歇根
- You can come with me.
- To Michigan?
但愿你能说服她搬家
Good luck
convincing her to move.
Fiona?
Estefania  天呐  你妻子
Estefania, dammit, your wife.
男人一声中有几件事是非常重要的
A man has few things
of real value in this life.
他的家庭 他的言出必行
His family.
The value of his word.
你说话算话么
Are you a man of your word?
你不住在这儿了
You don't live here anymore.
我还能指望你么
You still someone I can trust?
Mickey就要结婚了 你不在乎这事么
Mickey getting married.
Does that make sense to you?
她在按摩院工作
She works at Garden Spring Spa,
如果你把随便给别人口活 也叫“工作”的话
if you call jerking off
random dudes "working."
Terry让Mickey上她 好把他掰直
Terry made Mickey fuck her
to fuck the gay out of 'em.
我知道他和我在一起时的感觉
I know what he felt with me.
他伪装不了的
You can't fake that.
-你撞了谁?  -学校的一个女生
- What'd you hit?
- Girl at school.
我当时对Karen很不好
I wasn't very nice to Karen.
她收到你的短信时很开心
She was so happy
when she got that text from you.
短信？
Text?
出事故那晚她正要去见你
The night of the accident
when she came to meet you.
你要珍惜Mandy
You're taking Mandy
for granted.
她人好 为你着想
She's kind.
She's devoted.
你不能对她 招之则来挥之则去
She's not someone
whose feelings you can ignore.
我们要做最坏的打算么
Should we be
planning for the worst?
我也看见过奇迹发生
I've seen miracles.
They do happen.
坚持唤醒她
Keep engaging her.
想办法让她知道你们在这
Let her know you're here.
你是个王子 Jody
You're a prince, Jody.
不过我想 你是她的王子
I think that you're her prince.
我抢走了她的王子
I took her prince.
她相信真爱之吻
She believed
in the kiss of true love.
无耻之徒字幕组倾情奉献
[High Strung's
The Luck You Got]
♪ ♪
翻译 madao 大胖神
♪ Think of all the luck
you got ♪
翻译 木木 Yuhao
♪ know that
it's not for naught ♪
翻译 Yoki 胡小贼
♪ You were beaming
once before ♪
总校对  爱小花的胡小贼
♪ but it's not like that
anymore ♪
后制 大胖神
♪ What is this downside ♪
♪ that you speak of? ♪
♪ What is this feeling ♪
♪ you're so sure of? ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Round up the friends
you got ♪
♪ know that
they're not for naught ♪
♪ You were willing
once before ♪
♪ but it's not like that
anymore ♪
♪ What is this downside ♪
♪ that you speak of? ♪
♪ What is this feeling ♪
无耻之徒字幕组倾情奉献
♪ you're so sure of? ♪
哦 天啊
Oh, Jesus.
你睡觉的时候像个兔宝宝
You look like a baby rabbit
when you sleep.
这正是每个男人都想
Exactly what every man
wants to hear
在早上第一时间听到的事情
first thing in the morning.
你醒很久了
You awake long?
有一会儿了
A while.
这整个安娜堡（密歇根城市）的事情
This whole Ann Arbor thing--
我们都搞的定的
we can make it work.
我研究了一下
Been doing some research.
Worldwide Cup在Canton市有办事处
Worldwide Cup has an office in Canton
距离校园才18英里
only 18 miles from campus.
-喔  -是啊 对吧
- Wow.
- I know, right?
我看那里招不招人
I'm gonna see
if they need help.
而且那里的公立学校
And the public schools there
比这里的好多了
are a hell of a lot better.
我打给了一堆学校
I called a couple.
他们真接了电话
They actually
answered the phone.
他们说Debbie和Carl可以在年中转过去
They said that Debbie and Carl
could transfer mid-year.
他们人很好
They're so nice about it.
我不想让孩子们因为离开学校的朋友们
I just don't want
the kids resenting me
而生我的气
for making them
leave their friends at school.
什么朋友 Lip要毕业了
What friends?
Lip's graduating.
我不知道Ian怎么想
I'm not sure what to do
about Ian yet,
不过等他好点儿再去问他吧
but I'll ask him
when he's feeling better.
-那这房子呢？  -转租出去吧
- And the house?
- Sublet it, maybe.
还没想好呢
I don't know yet.
喔 我说 你转变的真快啊
Wow. I mean,
you've really turned a corner.
是啊
Yeah.
-早 -恩
- Morning.
- Mm.
你昨晚都没上床睡
You never
came to bed last night.
恩 是 不好意思 我昨晚看
Yeah, no, sorry,
I got sucked into, um...
赞比亚女拳击赛入迷了
Zambian women's boxing.
肌肉女让我觉得很搞笑
Muscular women
make me feel funny.
听着不错
Sounds hot.
你能快点准备么
Can you hurry up and get ready?
我今天想早点到学校
I want to get to school early.
好去餐厅顺几包薯块
Gonna swipe
some bags of tater tots
在Mickey的婚礼上用
from the cafeteria
for Mickey's wedding.
好 我这就起来
Okay, I'll be right up.
不好意思起来晚了 同志们
Late start this morning, guys.
-不好意思让你一个人弄了 -哦 谢谢 Debs
- Sorry, you're on your own.
- Oh, thanks, Debs.
我们花生酱吃完了
We're out of peanut butter.
Ian今天还请假在家么
Is Ian staying home
from school again today?
恩 是 他胃还疼呢
Yes, he is.
His stomach is still messed up.
- 还有蛋卷了么 -Carl都吃完了
- Any more pop tarts left?
- Carl finished them.
-他吃了三个 -我正长身体呢
- He ate three.
- I'm a growing boy.
小Broski带着我们的大男孩用大男孩马桶了
"Little Broski" took a big-boy
dump on the big-boy toilet!
Hey! Mwah!
我们要去商店买点纸尿裤
We're gonna celebrate
by walking to the store
庆祝一下吧
for some butt wipes.
还有花生酱和小蛋卷
And peanut butter
and pop tarts.
还有卫生棉  不好意思
And tampons. Sorry.
还有别忘了给他戴上帽子 外面冷了
And make sure he wears a hat.
It's getting cold.
-卫生棉？ -拜 伙计们
- Tampons.
- Bye, family!
拜 Fiona 打起精神 哥们儿
Bye, Fiona!
Butch it up, dude.
哥们儿
Dude.
你总得起来吧
You gotta get up at some point.
我脑袋都乱了 我--
I'm losing my mind. I--
我不停想这个婚礼的事
I can't stop thinking
about the wedding.
好 我最后再说一次
All right,
last time I'm gonna say it.
帮你自己一把
Do yourself a favor.
离那家人越远越好
Stay as far away from that
car wreck as humanly possible.
犯不上
Okay?
It's not worth it.
你下午能去礼堂帮我准备一下么
Can you help me set up
this afternoon at the VFW?
呃 不行 那个 我答应了要去Shela家
Uh, no, you know what?
I promised I'd go to Sheila's.
你知道 Karen今晚出院
You know,
Karen's getting home tonight.
-我去帮忙安置一下 -我去帮忙
- Gotta help set up.
- I'll help.
-你确定 -是
- You sure?
- Yeah.
嘿 等下 哥们 你不是该病着吗
Hey, wait, dude,
aren't you sick?
我就不明白 为什么Jody和Sheila
I don't get why Jody and Sheila
自己不能安排好Karen的破事儿
can't set up
Karen's shit by themselves.
听着 她还需要准备很多东西呢
Look, she needs
a lot of stuff, okay?
她自己都走不了路
She can't even
walk by herself yet.
她是脑前叶损伤
She's got frontal lobe damage.
撞她的那人
The dude who hit her
估计连个擦伤都没有
probably doesn't even
have a scratch on him.
♪ I turn to stone ♪
♪ I can't go on ♪
♪ I'm so alone without you ♪
♪ it ended so ♪
♪ can't take the toll
without you ♪
♪ ♪
走开 这是我的地方
Go away.
This is my turf!
你的地方 这是什么 “西线故事”么
Your turf?
What is this,West Side Story?
你不能占一整个车厢 这是公共财产
You can't own a whole train car.
It's public property.
我在这车厢睡了六年了
Sleeping in this car six years.
在这拉 在这吐 在这打飞机
Pissed, puked, jizzed in it.
根据体液法规 这就是我的地方
By law of bodily fluids,
it's mine.
反正我不走
Well, I'm not moving.
停下
Stop it!
你这个糟糕的流浪汉
You're a terrible
homeless person.
我不是流浪汉 我有家
I'm not homeless.
I have a home.
那昨晚你怎么不回去睡
Then why didn't you
go there last night?
我正要回去
I was on my way there
不过坐下后我不小心睡着了
when I sat down here
and accidentally fell asleep.
扯淡 你看着就像个乞丐 闻着也像个乞丐
Bullshit. You look like a bum,
you smell like a bum.
我是乘客
I'm a passenger.
离开我的专座
Get off my lawn.
好
All right!
我走
I'm going!
回我家去 在那里我是个
To my house, where I live,
受人尊敬的人
like a respectable human being.
我用图钉和彩色曲别针
I have labeled
the quarterly reports
把近四年的
from the last four years
季度报告都做好标记了
with color-coded tabs,
stapled and collated.
并且每份都双面拷贝作为存档
And I've included double-sided
copies for the archive.
哦 干的好 大师
Oh, dang, maestro.
我想问一下 你知不知道
I was wondering
if you knew of any positions
密歇根的办事处有没有职位空缺
opening up
in your Michigan office.
恩 我可以问一下 你要走了
Uh, I could ask.
You leaving us?
我男朋友可能要去那里读医学院
My boyfriend might be
going to med school at U of M.
我们还没确定
We're not sure yet.
喔  那太好了
Wow. That's terrific.
你走了我们会很伤心的
We'll be sad to see you go.
我也是
Me too.
恩 不好意思
Uh, sorry.
不知道你这周末忙不忙
I don't know
if you're busy this weekend,
我们家有个木屋
but my family has a cabin.
也就在北边半小时的车程
It's like a half an hour drive
north of here.
我们每年秋天都去
We go every year
during the fall,
宿营啊 烤棉花糖什么的
we camp,
and toast marshmallows,
还喝个烂醉
and kinda drink our faces off.
靠 那--
Shit, so--
我这件事办的实在不对
I'm doing this really,
really badly.
我绝对是想邀请你们俩人
I am totally
inviting both of you
还有上次打棒球是带来的那群孩子
and the pile of kids you brought
to the softball game.
真的--他们上次玩的很开心 一共多少个孩子
Real-- they'd have a great time.
How many are there total?
两个大点儿的 两个十几岁的 还有个小娃娃
Two teens, two preteens,
and a toddler.
太好了 我是说 我们有多余的帐篷
Perfect, I mean,
we've got extra tents,
还有多余的保暖睡袋
we've got sub-zero
sleeping bags,
几个孩子可以住一个帐篷里讲鬼故事
the little ones share a tent,
大人们就可以在
tell ghost stories,
while the adults
火堆前喝喝酒
just get blitzed by the fire.
而且 那个 很多我们办公室的人都会去
And I mean, tons of people
from work usually come.
那好极了
It's great.
听上去不错
Sounds good.
我弟弟们可能要参加个婚礼
My brothers
might have a wedding,
不过我会问问剩下几个的去不去
but I'll check
with the rest of the gang.
好 告诉我
Yeah, cool. Let me know.
那是什么啊 Liam
What's that, Liam?
是不是世界上最烦人的绵羊
Is that the world's
most annoying sheep?
它说什么
What's he saying?
-喔  他们到了么  -谁们
- Whoa, are they there now?
- Who?
-移民署  -不是
- The INS.
- No.
那你为什么打给我
Then why are you calling me?
我买了双破鞋子 现在坏了
I have this stupid shoe
I bought, and it break.
然后我打给客服 但是他们听不懂我说什么
And I tried to call to complain,
but they don't understand me.
你打给他们 行不
You call, yeah?
不行 Estefania 这是紧急号码
No, Estefania,
this number's for emergencies.
我无聊了 Steve
I'm bored, Steve.
我能做的就是坐在这上网 出去购物
All I do, I sit here
with textbooks, go shopping,
和鸡鸡很小的饥渴男上床很不开心
I get bad sex with horny boys
with tiny pintinhos.
我晚点儿去商店
I will go to the store later.
-来这儿 -好 好
- Come over.
- Okay, okay.
得挂了 给 给 给
Gotta go.
Here, here, here.
看那是什么 Liam
What's that? What's that, Liam?
是不是只小猪猪 一个又脏又臭的绞肉机
Is that a piggy? A filthy,
snorting bacon machine?
喔  你能学奶牛和小鸡么
Wow. Can you do
cows and chickens too?
没有你妈学的像
Not as good as your mom.
这有你的信
I have your mail.
有线账单 公益管理 房租 你的支票簿 签名吧
Cable, utility, rent.
Your checkbook. Sign?
还有你的个人信件
I have personal things
for you as well.
电视指南 建筑大观 瑞丽
TV guide, architectural di--
anthropologie.
这不是给女孩看的吗
Is that for girls?
我还收到了这个
I also have this.
密歇根大学的入学通知书
University of Michigan
enrollment notification.
一月份开课
Classes begin in January?
你私拆我的信件 这可是重罪
You opened my mail?
That's a felony.
这么说你劝Estefania和你一起搬走了
So you were able
to convince Estefania to move?
呃 呃
It's-- um--
我还在试 我正在处理 就别--
it's a work in progress.
I'm working on it. Just don't--
恩 我猜Fiona知道你的计划
Ah, but Fiona's
aware of your plans, I assume.
你开始越来越草率了
You're getting careless.
别
Don't.
时候不对？
bad time?
不是 只是提前弄这些孩子用的东西
No, just putting together
some baby stuff way prematurely.
怎么了
- What's up?
恩 我需要你的意见
Um, I need your advice.
恩 如果是关于孩子 大学 小鸡鸡的
Well, if it's about infants,
college, or tiny dicks,
你找错人了
I'm the wrong guy.
呃 不是 是
Uh, no, it's, um--
是关于疯女人的 你曾经娶过一个
it's about crazy.
You were married to once.
怎么 难道Mandy精神有点脱轨了
Why, is Mandy going
a little cuckoo for cocoa puffs?
是 我觉得是她开车把Karen撞了
Yeah, I think she ran over
Karen with her car.
什么
What?
我想 我想是她用车把Karen撞了
I think she-- she ran over
Karen with her car,
而且 而且她把这事给隐瞒下来了
and also she-- she carries this
like huge stockpile of arms--
等 等 等 等一下
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait.
你的现任女友
Your current girlfriend
开车撞了你的前女友
ran over your ex-girlfriend
with a car?
要点是正确 我是说
Signs point to yes.
I mean, I--
我不知道 我不知道她能耐有这么大
I don't know. I don't know
what she's capable of.
哥们 你要进入一级戒备了
Dude, you're at DEFCON 1.
你要想办法脱身
You need to get
the fuck outta there.
告诉我怎么做
Tell me how.
慢慢地
Very slowly.
你要让她觉得是自己的主意
You need to make her think
it's her idea.
一定要保持距离
Keep your distance.
因为一旦她们觉得自己被甩了
Because once they get
behind the wheel,
那你就没有退路了
there's no going back.
好 我经常得去那 你知道
Okay. I mean, I'm--
I'm-- I'm gone a lot, you know?
Karen那需要很多帮助 所以--
They need a lot of help
over at Karen's, so--
喔 喔  Lip 等一下
Whoa, whoa, Lip, wait, wait.
Mandy知道你要去那
Does Mandy know
you're going over there?
是啊 我告诉她的
Yeah.
Yeah, I mean, I told her--
Lip 你不能告诉她这破事儿啊
- Lip, you can't
tell her that shit!
这简直就是在疯牛面前摇红旗啊
That's like waving the flag
in front of the bull!
-那  -把车钥匙藏起来
- Well--
- Hide the car keys,
别显摆了 什么都不能告诉她
stop showering,
and you tell her nothing.
你做什么都不要说 Lip
And whatever you do, do not-- Lip.
不要让她怀上你的孩子
Do not let her bone you,
她们就是因为有了孩子才疯了的
because that oxytocin stuff makes them adhesive.
明白吗
You got it?
恩
Yeah.
我没打算和你说话
I'm not supposed to talk to you.
-Fiona和Lip会疯了的  -他们当然会
-Fiona and Lip will be mad. -Well, of course they will.
他们看我像是疯子 因为我是个坏爸爸
They treat me like a leper because I'm "a bad father."
没错
Yeah, right.
你根本没见过坏的父母
Tell you, you haven't seen bad parenting
你还没见过我老妈的光辉岁月呢
till you witness my mother in her glory days.
她有个惩罚之棍
Had this piece of wood she called a retribution stick.
一边是平的 一边是尖的
Flat side, skinny side.
如果我犯了小毛病 比如偷饼干
If I did something small, like steal an extra cookie
往她的浴缸里尿尿 她就用平的那头揍我
or piss in her shampoo bottle--whack. Flat side.
如果我犯了大事儿
But if I did something heinous,
在她睡觉的时候在床上点火
like set fire to her bed when she was napping,
或者让他在车库的赌博会上丢面子
or rat her out for her garage gambling ring,
她就会用尖的那头揍我了
the skinny side.
和抽鞭子一样
Like a whip.
但我没在她无家可归的时候
Whack! But did I throw that bitch
把她扔进臭水沟里 对吧
into the gutter when she needed a home? No.
我给她洗头 帮她洗松弛的奶子
I brushed her hair. I washed her saggy tits.
给他清理溃疡
I irrigated her ulcers.
我照料着他 直到他死
I nursed her all the way to the grave.
但你们却在我这么惨的时候无家可归
But you people, making me homeless in the dead of autumn?
我还帮你熬过了癌症 不是吗
After I got you through cancer?
昨天晚上 我在火车上睡的
I slept on a train last night!
很帅啊 我能试试吗
Cool. Can I try that?
那是种煎熬 我没地方去了
No! It's barbaric. I have no place to go!
你明白吗
Do you get it?
我可以让你溜进卡车里睡
I could sneak you in the van tonight.
你帮我
You'd do that for me?
你个胆小鬼
You little piker, you.
你来了
You made it.
椅子在那边  小心那些东西
Chairs are over here, and watch out for splinters.
Lip仍然还在和Karen鬼混
You know,,Lip is still up Karen's ass.
他还挺念旧的
It's getting old.
恩
Yeah.
Svetlana 她是个
So, Svetlana. She like, uh--
她不怎么爱说话
She's quiet.
很瘦 这个很奇怪
And skinny, which is weird,
因为她经常被大鸡吧操
'cause he usually bags fat chicks.
我为他洗衣
I do his laundry.
我帮他申请 Karen为他做了什么
I apply to colleges for him, and what the hell does Karen do?
除了会胡说八道 快他妈算了吧
Drools and farts. I mean, come on.
他喜欢她吗
Think he loves her?
她脑瘫了
She's brain-dead.
- 我说Mickey  - 我不清楚
- I mean Mickey. - I dunno.
无数人操过她
Tons of guys get chicks knocked up
但都没打算负责任
and don't get hitched, so...
老爸特别高兴这事  他计划的这些
Dad's super excited. Planned the whole thing.
他还从他的枪支俱乐部叫了些伙计
Invited his buds from the gun club.
有点意思
It's kind of sweet.
看看  这些是我工作时候偷的
Hey, look what I stole from work.
3杯卡布奇诺
Three cheers for Captain Cappuccino.
没拿点奶油什么的
Take some cream with that hostility?
没 这就不错了了  我刚刚告诉我最好的朋友
Oh, no, it's fine, just whisk my best friend off
我们想要个孩子的事  没什么大事
when I'm about to have a baby,no biggie.
你还告诉别人了吗
Whoa, we're telling people already?
不是别人 只有V
Not "people." Just V.
我老板Mike打算提拔我
And Mike from work, who says he'll look into transferring me.
别把你的裤子弄湿饿了  暗指 潜规则
Oh, don't get your panties in a wad.
我可不是大嘴巴
I know how to keep my mouth shut.
我真的很替你高兴  我只是觉得我有点惨
Look, I'm happy for you. I'm just sad for me.
不用担心
Oh... don't worry,
我们会每个月都回来看你的孩子的
we'll come visit your li'l peanut once a month.
或者你们可以和我呆一起
Or you could come stay with us.
我今天在网上看到4 5个房子
I found a couple four and five bedroom houses online today.
比芝加哥都便宜
Cheaper than Chicago.
披萨
Pizza!
趁热吃来吧
Come get it while it's hot!
-披萨  -香肠
- Pizza! - Pepperoni!
学校咋样
How was school?
我们分班了
We did fractions today.
好好吃你的饭
Chew your food like a human.
老板Mike
So, Mike from the office
这周末打算弄个露营什么的
is planning this big camping trip this weekend,
他邀请我们去
and we're all invited.
你想去
You wanna go?
恩 我们能做点饼干吗
Yeah! Can we make s'mores?
- 有射杀浣熊吗  - 没有
- And shoot raccoons? - No.
想去吗
Interested?
我很喜欢去 可那全是小虫子
Love camping in theory, except for the bugs,
还得在脏了吧唧的地上睡觉
and the dirt, and the ground-sleeping.
可听着还是不错了
But yeah, sounds great.
咖啡要再等会
Well, caffeine addicts await.
再见 Jimmy大夫了
Bye-bye, Dr. Jim.
你们知道Jimmy
you guys know how Jimmy's thinking about
想回医学院上学吗
maybe going back to med school?
不知道
No.
好吧
Okay, well,
如果他去了
if he does,
是在密歇根
it would be in Michigan.
他要离开我们吗
He'd leave us?
或者我们跟着他去
Or we'd go with him.
可能吧
Maybe.
去密歇根 那我们怎么上学
To Michigan. What about school?
只是一年
Well, it'll only be for a year.
我们还没决定呢
And nothing's decided.
我只是让你们好好想想
I just want youto start thinking about it.
Frank呢 我们不能扔下他
What about Frank? We can't leave him here.
- 我们可以扔下他  - 但天变冷了
- Of course we can. - But it's getting cold.
他那个熊样会没事的
His thick layer of bullshit will keep him warm.
你好
Hello?
Jimmy不在这 你能留信息吗
Jimmy's not here right now.Can I take a message?
在哪啊
Oh, wow, where is it?
有多少间浴室
How many bathrooms?
工作室
A studio?
我会帮你告诉他的
I will pass that on.
是谁啊
Who was that?
Ann Arbor Rentals
Ann Arbor Rentals.
Jimmy申请的房子通过率
The application Jimmy put in went through.
什么是工作室
What's a studio?
单身公寓 Debs
It's a one-room apartment,
我记得你说还没决定呢
I thought you said it wasn't decided yet.
我们这么多人  一个屋怎么住
How are we all gonna fit in one room?
他们回来了
They're here! They're here!
回来了
They're here!
欢迎回家
Welcome home! Welcome home!
看看你 甜心
Look at you, sweet girl!
我去拿行李
I'm gonna go grab her stuff.
看看 你看起来好多了
Look at you. You look so much better.
你脸色恢复了
Oh, my gosh, the color's back in your cheeks.
你回家开心吗
Are you happy to be home?
恩 我
Yes. I--
这很漂亮 我记得
This place is nice. I remember.
你好 Lip
Hi, Lip.
你好
Hi.
我很抱歉外面没有装栏杆
I'm sorry we didn't install the rails outside.
还有点潮湿
It's just been so wet.
你饿吗 我做了些沙冰
Um, are you hungry? I made smoothies.
我给你拿点
I'll get you some.
来吧
Here we go.
这是什么
What is this?
沙冰
It's a smoothie.
Ahh...
我挺喜欢喉咙凉凉的感觉的
I like the cold on my throat.
还有舌头上的味道
And the tongue-taste.
这是什么
What is this?
这个是冰沙
Well, it's a smoothie.
晚安了
Mm, good night.
Ron医生说这是怎么回事
What did Dr. Ron
say about this?
她只记得以前的事
She still has
most of her old memories,
新的东西 她记不起来
she just can't form
any new ones.
我从医院拿了点书
Got some pamphlets
from the hospital.
好的 谢了
Yeah, thanks.
她什么时候会好呢
Um, when's it go away?
每个人的情况都不一样 你知道的
Everyone's different, you know?
可能是永远这样了 可我觉得还是有希望的
Could be permanent,
but I say we keep hope alive.
我Sedona有个家
I got family down in Sedona.
他们在那治这种病
They have
healing vortexes out there.
选择性的治疗和恢复
Alternative treatments
and stuff.
她才回家
Oh, she just got home.
我们只是不知道 她想要什么而已
We don't know
what she needs yet.
她现在看起来好多了
She seems nicer though.
你把你电话落家里了
You left your phone at home.
你不用专门拿过来给我的
You didn't have to come down
here to bring it to me.
- 你有个怪怪的电话  - 谁打来的
- You got a weird phone call.
- From who?
一个租房子的女的打来的
Some lady from a--
from a rental place.
她说你的信用卡被核对成功了
She said your credit's
been approved.
你可以随时去签你要租的工作室的合同了
You can sign your contract on
your studio whenever you want.
看起来是我们都住在一起有点太挤了
Seems like a tight squeeze.
I mean, all of us in one room.
我是在我们讨论这事之前填的租屋意向
I filled out that application
form before we talked.
大学里基本上什么也没有
There was hardly anything
available on campus,
而且那个房子看着也不错
and it seemed like
a good opportunity.
所以你向银行借钱了
So you put a deposit down.
他们检查我的信用额度是理所当然的
I had to for them
to run the credit check.
你贷款就是为了租个工作室
On a studio apartment.
好吧 我承认这事我没考虑好
Okay, I guess I didn't
think it through.
你说什么  你已经准备要回去上课了吗
What, have you signed up
for classes already?
我基本上算是入学了吧  可也没全完事
Technically, I'm enrolled,
but it's complicated
- 因为我还在拖着
- 'cause of my deferral.
我觉得你应该休息一下了
Now might be a good time
for a little break-o.
所以 你就已经要这么去了呗
So, you're going,
just like that?
我说了  还没确定呢
Like I said, nothing's final.
可你说了  你没想带我们走
But you had
no plans to bring us.
你一直在偷偷摸摸的背着我们干这事
You've been slowly
backing away all along.
你好好想想吧
Think about it.
我自己一个人过去
Isn't it so much easier
if I get a place over there
周末再回来陪你们 是不是简单多了
and come home on the weekends?
我是想  为什么要全家都过去呢
I mean, why uproot
the entire family?
- 我真不敢相信你说出这样的话  - 不过就是4个小时的火车
- I can't even believe this.
- It's a four-hour train ride!
那可是他妈的整整一年啊
For one year,
it's totally doable!
你没问我的意见 就做了主
You made the decision
without me,
就好像这事对我们一点影响都没有一样
as if it has
absolutely no effect on us.
好吧 你决定要这帮孩子的监护权的时候
Okay, and how is that
any different from what you did
不也是这样吗
when you decided to become
legal guardian of those kids?
你压根就没想过我的想法
You never once considered
how I'd be affected.
- 那帮孩子是我的命 - 他妈的不是这回事 Fiona
- Those kids are my life.
- No shit, Fiona.
你只要问我一下  我也会告诉你 我支持你
And maybe if you would've
asked me, I woulda said, "yes.
我们一起养活这帮孩子吧  可你压根就没问我
Let's do this together."
But you didn't.
你压根都没他妈的想问我
It didn't even
occur to you to ask me.
不是  从你认识我那天
No, you have known from day one
你就应该了解我是什么样的人
what you were
getting into with me.
好吧  是我他妈的走进了你的生活
Right, I got sucked
into your world.
我按照你的要求做
I bent to your rules.
我只是想我们能
I just assumed
that we'd eventually decide
像一般的情侣一样决定一些事
how to move forward together
like couples do,
可你压根就没想过我
but there never was "we!"
我一直以来都干了那么多
What have I been doing?
做饭 打扫屋子 洗衣服 住在他妈的一个贫民窟里
Cooking, cleaning, laundry,
living in a goddamn slum!
贫民窟
A slum?
你曾经让我感觉是一个可以依靠的人
You made me feel like I could depend on you,
-现在我的家成了贫民窟  -难道不是吗
- and now it's a slum? - Isn't it?
一个12岁的小姑娘用枪指着我抢走了我的钱 Fiona
I got robbed at gunpoint by a 12-year-old girl, Fiona!
那你为什么不他妈找个别的地方去住呢
Why don't you go find another fuckin' place to sleep!
比如一个工作室
A fucking studio!
啊 陈年老烟卷和臭鼬的尿味儿
Ahh. Old cigarettes and skunk piss.
给
Here.
-只剩这点边儿  -我们就只有这些了
- Just crusts? - That's all they had.
那么 早饭有着落吗
Well, what about breakfast?
儿啊
Son...
我希望你永远不要知道
I hope you never have to know
无家可归的滋味
what it's like to not have a home.
他们放下这件事的 最起码Fiona会
They'll get over it. At least Fiona will.
我可不抱什么指望了
I wouldn't count on it.
这坏脾气的小娘们怀恨在心
That ornery bitch can hold a grudge.
人就是这么操蛋 这就是生活
People fuck up. That's life.
家人应该是永远的
Family is supposed to be forever.
不管你做了什么 都该关心你
Supposed to take care of you regardless of what you do.
这才是重点 否则何必呢
That's the whole point, otherwise why bother?
该死
Christ!
这有虫子
There are vermin in here!
我是你的家人
I'm your family.
你是对的 儿子 你从不会抛下我
You're right, son. You haven't let me down.
我在你这个年纪的时候
When I was your age,
我爸爸带我第一次去抢劫
my papa took me on my first heist.
我们搞到一台hi-fi音响，大概值600块
We scored a hi-fi stereo, about 600 bucks.
我们在酒店订了间房
Booked a hotel,
点了所有的客房服务还看了付费小黄片
blew all the dough on room service and porn.
这是我为当初付出的代价
This was back when you had to pay for it.
伙计 那些日子都过去了
Man. Those were the days.
这些年来我再没想过这些事
I haven't thought about that in years.
我的基佬养父有很多好东西
My foster gays have a lot of nice stuff.
你的基佬养父
Your foster gays?
Cassius和Lanier
Cassius and Lanier.
你这是在
Are you suggesting...
我能认为你这是在暗示什么吗
what I think you're suggesting?
-他们都有些啥  -有iPod 电脑
- What do they got? - iPods, computers...
-他们什么时候呆在那里  -他们周末上班
- How often they there? - They work weekends.
-你能搞定门锁吗  -我有他们的安保密码
- Can you pick a lock? - I have their security code.
这样说来
Is that so?
就这样吧
That's all right.
♪ Well, I can't stand still ♪
♪ you got me in a spin ♪
♪ you know, I can't stand still ♪
♪ you don't forget,oh, such a spin ♪
♪ the meanest shake that I could have ever been ♪
♪ you know that I'm struggling ♪
♪ to pick myself off the floor ♪
太阳出来啦 我们去野营
Rise and shine. We're going camping.
带上点保暖的衣服 好吗
Pack some warm clothes, okay?
晚上呆在湖边会感冒的
Gets cold by the lake at night.
你和Jimmy讨论过工作室的事儿了么
Did you talk to Jimmy about the studio yet?
没 我们走吧
No. Let's go.
早上好
Good morning.
我们要出发了 快起来
Let's go. Up and at 'em.
早上好啊 小奶球
Good morning, milk dud!
嘿 我们要去野营啦
Hey! Hi! We're going camping!
你想要去吗 好玩极了
You want to go camping? It's so fun.
大家一起游戏 唱歌 还有好多小孩
There's playing, and singing, and kids.
这有块脏的 哦你这小邋遢
And there's dirt. Oh, you love dirt!
我能动你的耳朵吗 你还是讨厌这么做吗
Can I do your ears,or do you still hate that?
别碰耳朵
My ears.
Jody在哪儿
Where's Jody?
他去了王太太家 把Hymie接过来
He's at the Wongs', picking up Hymie.
你还记得Hymie吗
Do you remember Hymie?
我记得 那个小蒙古人
I remember.The Asian mongoloid.
实际上我们可以叫他傻子
Actually, we can call him a retard.
只要我们不是歧视他就可以
We've earned that right.
你想和他呆一会吗
Do you want to spend time with him?
好的
Yes.
那可太棒了
Oh, that's wonderful.
他非常特别
He is so special.
你知道 我那天看了一部电影
You know, I saw this movie the other day
是关于世界各国的婴儿们的
about babies around the world.
你知道那些非洲的母亲
Do you know that mothers in Africa
会把孩子放在膝头来擦他们的脏屁屁么
wipe their babies' dirty bottoms on their knees?
-Jody在哪儿  -在王太太家
- Where's Jody? - At the Wongs'.
然后她们会用树叶来擦掉粑粑
And then they use leaves to scrape the poop off.
我想说 那为什么不一开始就用树叶包住好了
I mean, why not just use the leaves in the first place?
我不明白为什么待在一个全是细菌的
I don't understand why they're not
地方一点也不会让他们恶心
sick all the time over there with all that bacteria.
细菌
Bacteria.
我饿了
I'm hungry.
做完这些我就去做三明治
I'll make sandwiches after this.
Jody在哪儿
Where's Jody?
我明白了
I understand.
-Jody  -喔
- Jody. - Aww.
没事儿了老妈 让我来
It's cool, mom, I got this.
好了 大家准备好了没
Okay, we ready?
我找不到手电筒了
I can't find the flashlights.
看看橱子里
Check the closets.
我已经找了 找了得三遍了
Yeah, I did, like, three times.
- Carl在哪儿  -他说他不去了
- Where's Carl? - Said he's not going.
他不太舒服
He doesn't feel well.
哦 你脸色可真差
Oh, you look like garbage.
你病了
You sick?
没发烧
No temperature.
需要我们留下么
Should we stay home?
-不用 我没那么厉害  -别别别 求你了
- No, I'm not that sick. - No, no, no, please...
我们还是走吧 Liam会伤心的
Can we still go? Liam will be so sad.
好吧 但你得在床上躺好 喝点儿流质食物
Okay, but stay in bed. Drink fluids.
嘿 你能抱他一会么
Hey, can you hold him for a second?
好 好 好
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
拿上我的外套
Get my coat on.
好 好好参加婚礼
Okay. Enjoy the wedding.
迫不及待要听你们汇报了
I can't wait to hear the reports.
天呐 Ian
Jesus, Ian.
你昨晚几点回来的
What time did you get in last night?
-3点  -你去哪儿了
- 3:00. - Where were ya?
出去了
Out.
-真恶  -好吧
- Ew, gross! - Okay.
来吧 上楼 多睡一会
Come on, upstairs. Sleep it off.
有没有人能告诉我
Will someone please tell me
这孩子发生了什么事
what the hell is going on with that kid?
我想他准备说的时候会告诉你的
I'm sure he'll tell you when he's ready.
但愿如此
I hope so.
-好 我们走了  -恩
- Okay, we are off. - Okay.
再见
Bye.
再见 Debs
Bye, Debs.
-拜  -拜拜
- Bye! - Bye!
拜拜
Bye!
亲近大自然
Nurture nature!
我们一周都没嘿咻了
We haven't had sex in over a week.
对 我 恩
Yeah, I've, uh...
最近有点分心
been a little distracted.
这他妈要干嘛
What the fuck?!
-不管你做什么  -嘿
- Whatever you do... - Hey--
不管你做什么
Whatever you do...
千万别  千万别
do not... do not...
射在她里面
let her bone you.
嘿
Hey--
你的属于这里
You belong here...
属于我
with me.
不是属于那个该死的植物人
Not with that fucking vegetable.
啊
Aah!
伙计 谢谢你留我过夜
Hey, man, thanks for letting me crash.
你就这么来了 所以
Well, you just sorta showed up, so...
我们昨晚出去的时候是几点
What time did we crap out last night?
我十一点上的床
I was in bed by 11:00.
你是在3点之后过来的
You must have passed out after 3:00,
因为我在那时听到浴室的门响
'cause that's the last time I heard the bathroom door slam.
响了大概有五次 一次比一次声音大
Time five out of five, each time louder than the last.
恩
Hmm.
我很抱歉伙计 我弄得一团糟
I'm-- I'm sorry, man. I'm a mess.
-我昨天狠狠吵了一架和  -和你的女朋友
- I got in this huge fight with-- - With your girlfriend.
我们昨天聊这个话题聊了两个小时
We talked about it for two hours straight.
哦 呃 现在几点了
Oh. Uh, hey, what time is it?
1:30 我得走了 我下午 下午轮到我上班
1:30. I gotta split. I'm on, uh, afternoon rotation.
你自便就好
You may as well finish that.
这扇门用力点关就能锁上
This door locks behind you if you pull it hard,
-你能搞定 所以  -好的
- which you're awesome at, so... - Okay.
嘿 呃 小凯 是Lip
Hey, uh, Kev, it's Lip.
恩
Um...
听着 我搞砸了 我
look, I fucked up. I, um--
我内射了
I let her bone me. Just--
听到留言之后马上打给我 好么
call me back as soon as you get this, all right?
-你还好吗  -没事
- You okay in there? - Yeah.
你确定
You sure?
对 我只是 有点便秘
Yeah, I'm just, uh, a little backed up.
用了45分钟
For 45 minutes?
对
Yup.
-我能帮你点什么吗  -不用了
- Can I get you anything? - No, please.
我 我很好 明白吗 我没事 谢了
I'm-- I'm great. Okay? I'm fine. Thank you.
噢那太 看来你玩的很开心
Oh, very ni-- I will take that as a yes.
你的孩子们呢
- Where's your peeps?
那个小红毛是我妹妹Debbie
little redhead is my sister Debbie,
那个挂着鼻涕的小棕宝宝
and the little, brown baby with the boogers
是我弟弟Liam
is my brother Liam.
不错 不错 就这些吗
Nice, nice. Is that it?
呃 还有一个弟弟Carl生病了
Uh, yeah, my brother Carl's sick,
一个弟弟Ian昨晚喝醉还没醒
my brother Ian has a hangover,
还有另一个弟弟Lip正在举行婚礼
and my other brother Lip had that wedding.
了解了 了解了
Gotcha, gotcha.
你男朋友呢
Where's your man?
这杯是免费的
Is that cup a perk?
还是要自己付钱
Or did you have to pay for that?
嘿 别因为我有点钱就讨厌我
Hey, don't hate 'cause I get swag.
我是一个全职人员好吗
Okay? I'm a full-timer.
如果你不是要去密歇根
If you weren't moving to Michigan,
- 说不定你也能赚一大笔 - 真该死
- maybe you'd pull cups too. - Well, shit.
这能赚大钱了 我可怎么走啊
How can I go now knowing that?
哦真该死 我不该这么说
Well, shit, I don't think you can.
干杯
Cheers.
嘿 上车
Hey. Hop in.
我捎你一程
I'll give you a ride.
Nando 嘿 天哪 你什么时候来的
Nando! Hey, wow! When did you get here?
刚刚
Early.
你
You f--
你从巴西飞过来的
flew all the way from Brazil?
迈阿密
Miami.
我在那边处理生意
I was there on business.
我有点饿了 咱们去吃饭
I'm ravenous. We go eat?
♪ She brought it down
from the big, big hill ♪
♪ shine your diamonds,
shine 'em, shine 'em ♪
♪ placed it
on your windowsill ♪
♪ shine your diamonds,
shine 'em, shine 'em ♪
♪ that cobra's
in the cave with you ♪
♪ shine your diamonds,
shine 'em, shine 'em ♪
我想要个男朋友 你说我是个废物
you call me a punk for wanting a boyfriend or whatever,
那个人靠睡男人维生 你却要娶她
but you're gonna marry someone who screws guys for a living?
谁他妈在乎
Who gives a shit?
那就是一张破纸
It's a fucking piece of paper.
对我来说不是
Not to me.
嘿 别这样-- 听着
Hey, come on-- look.
我要结婚了
Just 'cause I'm getting hitched
不代表我们不能在一起了
doesn't mean we can't still bang.
对吗
Okay?
好了吗
All right?
如果你对我有一点点在乎 Mickey
If you give half a shit about me, Mickey--
诶 诶
Hey, hey.
一点点
Half.
就别结婚
Don't do this.
这个楼梯通向偏房
And these stairs lead to the side room,
然后这个是去卧室的过道
and this is the hallway to the bedroom.
这个是外面的桌子
This is the outside deck.
这是客厅 这是厨房
The living room, the kitchen,
另一间卧室 还有前厅
the other bedroom,and the front room.
老天爷啊 这个地方有多大
My God, how big is this place?
- 很大 - 混蛋
- Big. - Bastards.
没有棉花糖了
There's no more marshmallows.
我讨厌这个
I hate that.
这么一大包里面只有十个
They give you, like, ten in the whole bag.
- 如果他们抓到我们了怎么办 - 往好处想
- What if they catch us? - Visualize success.
如果他们采集到指纹怎么办
What if they dust for fingerprints?
我们一直戴着手套 找到一个
Always wear gloves. Got one.
这是个小宝箱 是个好兆头
It's a treasure chest. That's a good omen.
那要是DNA测验怎么办
What about DNA testing?
这种小盗窃 没人会用那种CSI的破玩意
Nobody bothers with that CSIcrap, not on a burglary.
(CSI:犯罪现场调查)
那些警察不会管这些偷鸡摸狗的屁事的
Cops'll see these faggots, they won't give three wet farts.
跟我干吗
Are you with me?
好吧 一 二 三 走你
Okay, one, two, three, go.
呃 下次再来吧
Eh, we'll get it next time.
你还一口没动呢 Steve
You haven't taken one bite, Steve.
这些好吃的都浪费了
All this food going to waste.
好吧 跟我说说
Now, tell me...
我听说的 关于医学院的事
I hear reports of, um, medical school.
我一月份回学校
Uh, going back in January.
以后可能会成为一名皮肤科或者外科大夫
I'm gonna become a dermatologist or a surgeon.
不错
Good.
外科整形现在很吃香
Cosmetic surgery's a rich field.
非常有钱途 很有潜力
Very lucrative. Much potential.
十分正确
Indeed.
但这个需要你搬到另一个州去
And this would require a move to another state.
只是暂时的 我--我还在敲定细节
Only temporary. I'm-- I'm still working out the details.
你知道的 我 我真的只是想
You know, I-I really just want to do
做一些造福大家的事
what's best for everyone.
这可听着像是你想
Well, it sounds like you want to do
做一些造福自己的事
what's best for yourself.
呃 但对Estefania来说有个
Uh, but having a doctor husband for Estefania
做大夫的丈夫是件好事
would be a great thing.
在美国 医生们都是英雄
You know, in America, doctors are seen as heroes.
我对你们的文化很了解
I'm familiar with your culture.
但重点是
But the point being is it's--
这什么都很好 安娜堡是个很棒的地方
it's all good, you know? Ann Arbor's a great town.
那儿有很多商场
There's lots of shops.
你上次见我女儿是什么时候了
And when was the last time you've seen my daughter?
呃 两天之前
Uh, two days ago.
怎么了
Why?
三个小时之前我见到她了
I saw her three hours ago.
在移民规划局
In INS Holding.
我觉得你应该还不知道她已经被驱逐了
I suppose you're not aware she's being deported.
等等 为 为什么
Wait, why? Why--
昨天你错过了移民局的家访 Steve
You missed an INS visityesterday, Steve.
她为什么不给我打电话
Why didn't she call me?
她打了 你没接
Well, she tried. You didn't pick up.
而且她没能成功打动检查人员
And she failed to impress the authorities.
她甚至不知道你的生日
Didn't even know your birthday.
我的生日是圣诞节! 记住这个能有多难
My birthday is Christmas! How hard is that to remember?
还有你妈妈的名字
And your mother's name.
这是我的错吗 我们  我们都用卡片记过了
This is my fault? We did-- we did flash cards.
我不能时时刻刻在她身边
I can't be with her every second.
我对你要求很少 Steve
I ask so little of you, Steve.
就那么一点点
So little.
别惹麻烦
Stay out of trouble.
照顾好我女儿
Be attentive to my daughter.
她在这个国家的居住权是没有保证的
Her presence in this country is controversial.
你知道的
You understand that.
我们是活在显微镜下的 我以为你明白的
We were under a microscope. I thought I made that clear.
发生这事我非常抱歉
Look, I'm so sorry this happened,
我不知道应该怎么做才能防止它的发生
I just don't know what could've been done to prevent it.
这正是问题关键 不是吗 Steve
That's precisely the problem, isn't it, Steve?
现在怎么办
What now?
发生的事情没法回头
Well, what's done cannot be undone.
现在我必须到处给点好处
Now I must grease many palms.
事情才会解决的
It will be dealt with.
等等 所以你刚才的意思是
Wait, so you're telling me
你从来没去过脱衣舞俱乐部
you've never been to a strip club?
没有 光想想贴身舞
No. Just the thought of a lap dance
就已经让我神魂颠倒了
actually makes me woozy.
就像 你看我像在调戏人吗
Like, do I grope?
如果 怎么才能调戏她的同时不冒犯她
If-- how do I go about doing that in, like, a non-offensive way?
好比 要有眼神交流吗 或者
Like, do I make eye contact, or is that--
那应该是很冒犯她们的 我的意思是
that could be insulting, 'cause I mean,
她们在身体上下了那么大的功夫
she works so hard on her body.
哇 你真的是个绅士
Wow, you really are a gentleman.
我才不是个绅士
I am hardly a gentleman.
我只是对于被迫的亲密有些不接受
I just have a problem with forced intimacy.
怪我妈妈
Blame my mother.
你妈妈以前是个脱衣舞女
Your mom was a stripper?
现在也是
Still a stripper, by the way.
九十岁了
90 years old
她得花四十分钟解开内衣
Takes her like 40 minutes to unhook her bra,
但是她解的时候 真是场好戏
but when she does, what a show.
所以 呃
So, um...
我们好像是没去参加聚会
we sorta ditched the party.
是 确实是
Yeah, we sorta did.
我现在要说三个想法
I'm gonna make three assumptions.
说吧
Fire away.
好的 第一 你像我一样醉
Okay, one, you're as drunk as I am.
正确 嘘
Correct. Shh.
第二 你像我一样冷
Two, you're as cold as I am.
比你冷 我穿的少
Colder. Less padding.
忽略这个
I'm gonna ignore that.
第三
Three...
你也是个绅士
you're a gentleman.
错了
False.
正相反
Quite the opposite.
那么 你最好表现出来
Well, then you better behave yourself,
因为我还没有醉到不会邀请你
because I am way too drunk not to invite you
去我的帐篷
back to my tent right now.
该死的 Gallagher
God damn, Gallagher.
以后我得让你多生生气
I oughta get you pissed off more often.
所以 我们现在怎么办
So, what are we gonna do?
告诉大家都走吧
We gonna tell everyone to leave?
不
Nah.
我去解决了这件破事
I'll go get this shit over with,
你在这等我
and, uh, you can wait here for me.
不会超过一个小时吧
Shouldn't take more than an hour, right?
你最好准备好大战第二回合
You better be ready for round two.
你不想解决这件事对吧
You're not seriously going through with this, are you?
你为什么要表现出一副好像我有的选得表情
Why are you acting like I got a choice in this?
这全是他妈的放屁
This is bullshit.
听我说 Mickey
Listen to me, Mickey.
你爸爸是个恶魔 是个变态
Your dad is an evil, psychotic prick.
你想让他就这么毁了你一辈子
You're just gonna let him ruin your life?
你他妈应该学会长大了
You need to grow the fuck up.
别装的像你很了解我爸似的
Don't act like you know a thing about my dad.
你他妈搞笑呢吧
Are you fucking kidding me?
没有人能
Not everybody gets to just--
没有人会
not everybody just gets to
没人时时刻刻都他妈实话实说
blurt out how they fuckin' feel every minute.
大家都在找你
Everyone's looking for you.
我抽根烟 这也不行吗
I'm having a fuckin' smoke. Is that all right?
你刚到
You just get here?
是
Yeah.
我都不知道你要来
I didn't know you were coming.
临时决定的
Last-minute decision.
来吧
Come on.
♪ Dead man walking
like a wind-up toy ♪
♪ plodding, never plotting for
the things that bring him joy ♪
♪ living in the movies
like he's celluloid ♪
♪ and then it's over ♪
♪ so roll the credits now ♪
♪ dead man standing
single file in every line ♪
♪ gave up on the searching ♪
♪ he was scared
of what he'd find ♪
♪ but I don't wanna live
like I'm headed to the grave ♪
♪ no, I don't wanna
live that way ♪
♪ got a purpose and a plan ♪
♪ and I don't wanna live
like a dead man ♪
Ah!
什么 你还好吗
What, what? You okay?
我这是在干什么
What am I doing? What am I doing?
你想先暂停吗 我们可以的
Do you want to stop? We can stop.
-我很抱歉  -别这样
- I'm sorry. - Don't be sorry.
我们会好的 不是吗 即使发生了这些
We got carried away, all right? These things happen.
我不知道我在干什么
I don't know what I'm doing.
你在利用我报复
You're using me for revenge.
有吗
Am I?
我不是说我介意 我真的不介意
I'm not saying that I mind. I-I-I do not mind.
我只是确认下原因
I just recognize the impulse.
他计划丢下我一个人去密歇根
He was planning on going to Michigan without me.
混蛋
Oh, shit.
他装作好像要把我们都带走
He acted like he was gonna take all of us,
但这已经不是他第一次说谎了
but it's not even the first time that he's lied.
我又被他骗了
I closed my stupid eyes to it
因为我没想到到事情会这样糟
'cause I wanted it to work so bad.
你并不傻
Your eyes aren't stupid.
不 我就是个傻瓜
Oh, I'm an idiot.
只是有人骗了你
Just because someone dumps on you
并不意味着你不是个姑娘
does not mean you deserve it.
告诉我她什么时候骗过你
Tell me that when someone's dumping on you.
Eve?
那是我妻子
That's my wife.
前妻
Ex-wife. God.
我们上周就离婚了
Papers went through last week.
我太懦弱了 我都不敢把这个去掉
I'm kinda too chicken to get it removed,
所以我考虑换一个好一点的词
so I'm thinking about making it into a bigger word.
比如
Like, uh...
sleeve 也许
"Sleeve" maybe.
eleven吧 我不知道
"Eleven." I don't know.
我想你很庆幸她的名字不是Ocksucker
I guess you're lucky her name wasn't "Ocksucker."
的确
Yeah.
你什么时候发现出事了
When did you know when it was over?
当她开始每天去体育馆
When she started going to the gym every day.
你
You?
毫不犹豫
Without a hitch.
儿子 你做的好
Son, you did good.
把门关上 把门关上
Close the door. Close the door.
你觉得这些值多少
How much you think it's all worth?
不知道 3千也许
I don't know. Maybe 3 grand?
真的 够本了
- Really? - Damn straight.
好了 来庆祝吧
Hey, let's celebrate.
去给我们做点意大利面
Go cook us up some spaghettios.
听着 我知道我很草率
Lis-- listen, I know that I got sloppy, Nando,
但我会弥补的 告诉我该做什么
but I will fix it.Just tell me what I can do.
嗑药 偷车
Run-- run drugs, steal cars,
你知道 我爸爸和政府有关系
you know, my dad has connections in the government.
他很厉害的
He's a powerful man.
他支持着移民法案
He supported immigration legislation--
今天交通太堵了 是那些年轻人都出来玩吗
So much traffic today. Are the cubs playing?
你知道吗
It's-- you know what?
这是件好事 真的
It's a good thing this happened, actually.
我指的是 不完全的 当然
I mean, not entirely, of course,
但我对规矩很清楚
but I-I'm completely clear on the rules.
你知道 我百分之百和你一样
You know, I'm absolutely on the same page as you.
我是说 真的谢谢你
I mean, thank you for that. Truly. Truly.
来让我们看看那是谁
Oh, let's go see who that is.
我马上就弄完karen最喜欢的零食了
I'm just finishing up Karen's favorite snack.
snickerdoodle蛋糕
Snickerdoodle cupcakes.
她在楼下
She's upstairs.
嗯 不用你
Um, but hey, um, you don't need
去装移动灯
to install the motion lights
因为jody要带karen和hymie去赛多纳
because Jody is taking Karen and Hymie to Sedona
住在离漩涡很近的地方 所以
to live near the vortexes, so...
这没什么 他们将像一家人
It's fine. They're gonna be near family.
在那之后 她会成为他的妻子
And she is his wife, after all.
王女士同意她带hymie走吗
Is-- is Mrs. Wong okay with Hymie leaving?
当然 她是他妈妈
Well, she's his mother,
更何况孩子是属于妈妈的 所以
and babies belong with their mothers, so...
你继续 我会准备点零食
You go on up. I'll be right there with snacks.
你感觉怎么样
How you feeling?
你妈妈说你要走了
Your mom says you're moving.
我
I am?
是的 去亚利桑那
Yeah, to Arizona?
大峡谷
The Grand Canyon.
仙人掌
Cactuses.
是的
Right.
我知道你在这 现在是只有我们吗
I know you're in there. It's just us now, okay?
我们可以聊聊
We can talk.
你记得那天
you remember that day
嗯 我们喝醉了
we, uh-- we got drunk
绕着林肯公园跑
and, uh, ran around Lincoln Park
弄响了所有的普锐斯的报警器
setting off all the alarms on the Priuses?
是的
Yeah.
然后我们
And then we, um--
我们爬上了林肯雕像
we climbed the Lincoln statue
然后给老亚伯涂了点口红
and gave Old Abe some, uh, lipstick with red sharpie.
是的
Yeah... yeah.
嗯 你那时一点也不害怕
Yeah, you were, uh, fucking fearless.
完全像个疯子
And a total shithead.
我记得 那晚你让我平静下来
I remember, um, you made me go down on you that night
在本命顿的洗手间
in the bathroom of Bennigan's.
你都记得？
You remember all that?
是的
Yes.
但是
But...
我没有那种感觉了
I can't feel.
什么感觉
Feel what?
充实的
Stuff.
内心的充实
Inside.
我
I, uh...
我不知道你说的是什么
I don't know what that means.
我不知道
I can't explain.
但是
But...
没什么
it's okay.
这是那些零食吗
Are there snacks?
mandy做的
Mandy. Mandy did this. Okay?
是Mandy撞的你  是她毁了你
Mandy hit you with the car and fucked you up forever!
好吗 都是因为我
All right? Because of me.
Mandy Milkovich.
是的
Yes.
你明白吗
Do you understand me?
嗯
- Yes. - Okay.
你知道谁打了你吗
Do you know who hit you?
不知道
No.
是零食吗
Are there snacks?
♪ Lady in red ♪
♪ is dancing with me ♪
♪ cheek to cheek ♪
♪ there's nobody here ♪
Mandy!
过来
Come here.
别走 好吗
Couldn't stay away, could you?
你毁了karen 的生活
You ruined Karen's life!
你这个充满嫉妒的疯婊子
You're a jealous, demented cunt, Mandy!
真的
Seriously!
好了吗 我们分了吧
All right? We're done!
我为你做了这么多 你这个混蛋
I did it for you, you prick.
我为你做了所有事情 但你就是个白痴
I did everything for you, but you're so fucking blind.
你知道吗 别舍不得了
You know what, don't sweat it.
我们在你来之前就分了
We were done before you got here.
这是kenyatta
This is Kenyatta.
他在和我约会
He's my date.
我刚在卫生间干了一炮
I just swallowed his load in the bathroom.
你尝出来了吗
Can you taste it?
他结了
He did it.
他和一个女人结婚了
He got married. To a woman.
我告诉了你不要来好吗
I told you not to come here, okay?
你就这样干待着  当你爱的人
You try sitting on your ass while the person you love--
哦抱歉是你操的人
No, I'm sorry, I mean the guy you've been fucking
随便和一个混蛋结婚
gets married to some random commie skank!
混蛋
Fuckin' commie!
♪ You were amazing ♪
♪ never seen
so many people-- ♪
走吧
Let's go.
下车
Get out of the car.
好的
Okay.
这一回 像男人点
Be a man.Just this once.
看着我
Look at me.
深呼吸
Deep breath.
振作点
Chin up.
上船
Get onto the boat.
我可以打给fiona吗
Can I just make one phone call to Fiona?
可以吗
Please?
操
Fuck.
我知道不能
I don't think I'm gonna make it.
我们很近了
We're so close.
我想躺一下
I gotta lay down for a little bit.
停下来 别 我们要到了
Ian, hey, stop. No! We're here!
我想吐
I'm gonna puke.
我们知道你偷过
We know you've been stealing...
操
Fuck.
孩子 冷静点 我能帮你什么吗
- Kid, settle down. - Hey, whoa, can I help you?
你是谁
Who are you?
我是他哥哥 怎么了
I'm his brother. What's going on?
我们有理由相信这孩子
We have reason to believe this child
也许偷窃了他的养父母
may have robbed his former foster parents
当他们下午在工作的时候
while they were at work this afternoon.
是吗 你有什么证据
Yeah? What proof you got?
他有一个给他的特殊密码
He had a special security code assigned to him.
他是唯一知道这个的人
He's the only one that knows it.
很好 我只能说那不算证据
All right, as far as I can tell, that's not evidence.
把你的手给我他妈拿下来
Get your fuckin' hands off him, man.
他的密码是四个字母
His code was a series of four letters.
C-A-R-L.
把你的手给我拿下来
Take your fuckin' hands off him, man!
他就是个孩子
He's just a fucking kid!
好了够了
All right, that's enough of that.
退后 先生
Step back, sir.
把你手从警察身上拿开 现在
Take your hands off the officer right now!
离警察远点
Step away from the officer.
没事的
It's gonna be okay.
这个孩子偷了东西 对吧
This kid stole from people, all right?
-我们会带他走  -你真是 他是个孩子
- We're taking him in. - You're ta-- he's a fucking kid!
别碰警察
Do not touch the officer.
-立马退后  -carl 过来
- Step back right now! - Carl, come here!
如果你在干涉 我立马逮捕你
If you interfere again, I will arrest you!
别碰他
Do not touch him!
你为什么对他那么凶
Why are you being so rough with him?
你必须
You are gonna have to--
他他妈的干什么对他这么凶
Why is he being so fucking rough with him?
你再碰他一下试试  再碰他 我就抓了你
You touch him again, I will arrest you!
晚上好啊  先生们
Whoa, whoa. Good evening, gentlemen.
- 你是他们的父亲吗   -  没错 我是
- Are you the parent? - Why, yes, I am.
你他妈的在这干什么 Frank
What the fuck are you doing here, Frank?
我回家来待会
I'm coming home.
我们要去警局对你儿子问话
We're taking your son in for questioning.
不是他偷得  是我
He didn't do the heist, I did.
看到这鞋了吗  多闪啊 就是有点大
You see? Shiny, but a little bit big.
我还拿了一拖拉机的电子产品呢  那些玩意最好卖了
I also got a boatload of electronics-- those sold fast.
你们知道  芝加哥还有好几个24小时的典当行吗
Did you know that Chicago has several 24-hour pawn shops?
他没干  他是无辜的
He-- he didn't-- he's innocent.
是我逼他告诉我密码的
I forced him to give me the code.
不是吗  儿子  你告诉他们
Didn't I? Son, tell 'em.
我的天啊 他可是个老实巴交的孩子
Oh, my God. He's dumber than a bag of hair.
他连绷带都不敢自己拿下来  别说抢劫了
He couldn't pull off a band-aid, much less a robbery.
好吧  我站这
Okay, here.
趁着我还清醒点 把我拷上吧
Cuff me, before I get disorderly.
坚强点 儿子
Be brave, son!
随叫随到的客房服务啊
Order room service.
这是怎么了
What happened?
局子那地可冻死个人啊
Hell froze over.
♪ I... ♪
♪ am just a beggar ♪
我是Steve 留个信吧
Hey, it's Steve. Leave some words.
嗨  是我
Hey, it's me.
让5个孩子去医学院
Five kids at med school.
我脑子是怎么了
What was I thinking?
你没错 我们是住在贫民窟里
And you're right. We live in a slum.
也就是4个小时的火车  没什么大不了的
It's a four-hour train ride. That's nothing.
我们能挺过去的
We can make this work.
我们必须得挺过去
We have to.
我爱你
I love you.
给我打电话
Call me.
无耻之徒字幕组倾情奉献